<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sass on Bastien</title>
    <link>/en/tags/sass/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sass on Bastien</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 17:05:59 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/en/tags/sass/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Sortir Agen</title>
      <link>/en/realisations/sortir-agen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 17:05:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/realisations/sortir-agen/</guid>
      <description>The app was created with hybrid html5 with Cordova. This allowed me to combine the flexibility of Html5 and some native features like GPS location, adding events to the calendar and sharing on social networks.    Sorry, you don&#39;t have HTML5 video and we didn&#39;t catch this properly in javascript. You can try to view the gif directly: https://zippy.gfycat.com/CavernousVengefulDiscus.gif.      I created interactive maps with google API to discover walks, cultural activities and sports, bars and restaurants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fondation la dépêche</title>
      <link>/en/realisations/fondation-groupe-depeche/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 17:05:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/realisations/fondation-groupe-depeche/</guid>
      <description>Sorry, you don&#39;t have HTML5 video and we didn&#39;t catch this properly in javascript. You can try to view the gif directly: https://thumbs.gfycat.com/LinearUniqueAlligator-size_restricted.gif.      The biggest challenge was to adapt to the customer comebacks, doubts and many changes, including during the development phase, in very short deadlines.       The &#34;Occitanie Jobs&#34; section was the most complex to redesign. At first, the UX was not adapted to a smooth and clear navigation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SKLTN</title>
      <link>/en/realisations/skltn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2016 17:05:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/realisations/skltn/</guid>
      <description>I was searching for a solution to avoid some dumb repetitions at the beginning of a website project. Whether I create without a base or retrieve code I had already done before, I was always wasting time. I wanted to have a simple and flexible project base with only the components that I need. I came up with the idea to merge the great possibilities of the css pre-processor SASS and the power of Yeoman to give a helping hand to the start up of projects.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>